Someone poisoned Dexter Cornell. He's got to find out who. He's got to find out
why. He's got to find out now. In 24 hours, he'll be Dead On Arrival.
D.O.A. is a mystery, thriller film directed by Annabel Jankel.
Dexter Cornell, an English Professor becomes embroiled in a
series of murders involving people around him.
Dexter has good reason to want to find the murderer but hasn't much time.
He finds help and comfort from one of his student, Sydney Fuller.
Dexter Cornell, played by Dennis Quaid.
Sydney Fuller, played by Meg Ryan.
Mrs. Fitzwaring, played by Charlotte Rampling.
Hal Petersham, played by Daniel Stern.
Gail Cornell, played by Jane Kaczmarek.
Bernard, played by Christopher Neame.
is a 1988 American neo-noir  film directed by Rocky Morton and Annabel Jankel.
A remake of the 1950 film of the same name, it stars Dennis Quaid, Meg Ryan and
Charlotte Rampling, and was filmed in Austin, Texas and San Marcos, Texas.
It was theatrically released in the United States on March
18, 1988, to generally positive reviews.
The film explores themes of race against time, toxication,
literature professor, culprit, relationship.
The tone is intense and mind_bending.